http://www.nss-nrs.com/privacy-policy/

My NSS
(0)
(0)
Information and Data Collection
We collect only the minimum data needed to provide the services ordered and provide customer service correspondence. This data includes your name, shipping and billing address, email address, phone number(s), employment institution, licensure number(s), and academic designations. We will update, correct, or delete customer information on written request emailed to info@northernspeech.com. This information is only collected if you expressly provide it to us. We do NOT collect any identifiable information about you without your knowledge. We do NOT follow your browsing path outside of NorthernSpeech.com.
What Information Do We Collect Online? How Do We Use It?
In areas of our site, we ask you to provide information by filling out and submitting online forms. We only ask for the information needed to provide you with the services you request. For example, if you are taking an Online Course and want to receive ASHA credit, we have to ask for your ASHA account number because it is required by ASHA. In order to make improvements to our site, we may gather information that helps show how customers use the site. For example, we might do research to determine which areas are accessed most frequently. This information is analyzed only in aggregate and not at the individual level. Personal information, such as name and email address, is NOT included in the analysis.
How We Use Phone Numbers and Email Addresses
It is important that you provide us with a valid email address and phone number when you set up an account so that we may communicate with you. Your email will be used to communicate relevant account and ordering information. For example, after you place an order on our site, we use your email address to send an order confirmation with UPS tracking information, if applicable. You will also receive your Live Course registration confirmation via email and your notices that Online Courses are available. You will receive these emails only if you have provided your email address during checkout or as part of registering with the site. We will only call you in the event of an important message regarding your product shipment or with an urgent message about a change to a live seminar schedule.  We do NOT engage in telemarketing. We do NOT sell or share phone numbers or email addresses with other companies. We use email only as a means of giving you the information you need and receiving feedback from our customers. We encourage you to email us with your questions or comments. We read every email we receive.
Promotional Correspondence and Opt Out Policy
We may send you email and mail correspondence with special offers, sales, and information on new products, services, and courses. You may opt-out anytime if you wish to no longer receive these promotional emails, flyers, or postcards. To opt-out please send your written request emailed to info@northernspeech.com. You may also opt-out via the unsubscribe links found on all promotional emails.
We do purchase mailing lists and email rosters from third party licensing agencies and professional trade associations. Continued correspondence from us may arrive to you due to your mailing address or email being contained on these third party lists. We kindly request you contact these groups to have your information withheld from distribution as we do not have control over the content of these third party lists.
Sharing Your Information
We are the sole owner of information collected at NorthernSpeech.com. We do NOT share, release, sell or trade mailing addresses, email addresses, phone numbers, information collected as part of a survey, or specific details about you with any third parties for proprietary or data mining purposes. We do NOT contribute to or participate in shared or cooperative databases which give other companies access to your personal information. We use your personal information only to serve you and your needs, and we do everything possible to keep the information secure.
Data Security and Financial Transactions
The security of your personal data is very important to us. We employ reasonable technical and administrative safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal data. During credit card transactions, we protect transmission through the use of encryption such as the Transport Layer Security (TLS) protocol. We employ industry standard SSL (TLS 1.2 or newer) throughout the website. After the purchase transaction is completed, we retain the minimum information needed to provide customer support and for issuing credits and refunds. This retained information includes the last 4 digits of the credit card and the transaction ID from the payment processor.  We do NOT save or store complete credit card numbers at NorthernSpeech.com. Returning customers will be asked to again enter their credit card information at time of purchase. In the unlikely event we suffer a data breach, we will notify customers within 72 hours of the data breach.
Web Browsing, Cookies and Analytics
Like most websites, NorthernSpeech.com utilizes cookies to better optimize your browsing experience. A cookie is a very small file that is downloaded to your device when you visit a website. You may manage your cookie settings via your web browser's preferences. Turning off cookies will provide a decreased browsing experience and areas of our website may not function as intended. We partner with Google to analyze customer traffic and navigation patterns to and within our site. This data is not linked to your personal, identifiable data. We do not follow your browsing path outside of NorthernSpeech.com.
External Links and Privacy
NorthernSpeech.com does contain links to other websites, such as websites, blogs or social media pages of our product and course authors. We also often use YouTube to deliver video content at NorthernSpeech.com. Once you have navigated outside of NorthernSpeech.com to these third party websites, such as YouTube, your browsing experience, including the submission of personal information, will be subject to the individual privacy and data policies of those websites.
Children
We do not knowingly collect personal information nor knowingly send marketing correspondence to children under 18 years of age.
Information Pertaining to MBSImP.com
At the time of enrollment we collect the minimum data needed to provide the services ordered and provide customer correspondence.
We will update, correct, or delete customer information on written request emailed to mbsimp@northernspeech.com.
On successful training completion, your name, academic designations, employment institution, city, state/province/region or country will be published in the Find a Registered Clinician public registry. To request removal of your listing from this registry, please email request to mbsimp@northernspeech.com.
We will notify customers within 72 hours in the event of a data breach.
We may contact you with special promotions and sale offers. You may opt out of unsolicited correspondence at any time by sending a written request emailed to mbsimp@northernspeech.com. You may also opt-out via the unsubscribe links found on all promotional emails.
We do NOT ask for any financial information nor do we process credit card transactions at www.mbsimp.com.
We do NOT sell, trade, or share your personal, identifiable data with any third parties for proprietary or data mining purposes.
Analysis of website data in relation to personal, identifiable data may be used for customer support correspondence and internal quality control purposes. Website data is not released to any third parties for proprietary or data mining purposes.
Patient information entered into the Patient Data & Reports templates meets the requirements of de-identified as stated in 45 Code of Federal Regulations, Part 164.514b(2)(i) of the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA). This data is used for research purposes by outside entities. Your personal, identifiable data is not shared or included in this research.
×
Become a Peer Reviewer to take Courses for FREE!
×
NSS Email Alerts!
325 Meecher Rd.
